So a bunch of Israeli pro-famine activists are launching a counter flotilla to the Global Samud Flotilla to sail in front of the U.S. Embassy in Tel Aviv in an act of extreme performative activism.
Currently over 75 Israeli boat owners have already registered for Friday's flotilla, and they're pulling in friends.
The Israeli Yachting Association and boat companies are joining too.
So when I say things like the genocide in Palestine is a transnational war on the working class, this is kind of what I'm referring to.
So a bunch of moneyed colonial genocidal yacht owners are sailing in front of the embassy of their imperial daddy to just keep the violence going and make sure the ethnic cleansing is complete.
And let's talk about, like, the difference in material conditions, too.
So they've got yachts. They already have more boats than we do.
We've got these, like, barely seaworthy vessels that we cobble together in two months since the final solution was being enacted in Gaza,
attempting to establish a humanitarian corridor into a people facing annihilation for real estate interests, natural gas exploitation, and the list goes on.
So we're sailing with Baby Formula and Ancient Sea Hulks, and they're sailing in yachts to appeal to the imperial power structure that denies that Baby Formula.
So, like, I guess if you're looking for a better example of transnational class struggle, be hard-pressed to find a better one, Free Palestine.